Guide to the Georg Kreisel Papers SC0136
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Correspondence
  - Pravitz, 1982 Sep - Nov (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Prestel, 1982 Nov (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Renardel, 1982 Oct - Dec (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Rodenberg, 1982 Oct (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Sachs, 1982 Dec (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Salecker, 1983 Jan (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Schimanovich, 1982 Aug - Oct (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Schmerl, 1982 Jun (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Schmetterer, 1982 Nov - Dec (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Scott, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Shiner, 1982 Mar - Nov (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Sinaceur, 1982 Oct - Nov (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Stavi, 1982 Oct (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Stepanov, 1982 Nov (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Sundholm, 1982 Oct (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Takeuti, 1982 Jun - 1983 Jan (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Taussky-Todd, 1982 Oct - Dec (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Tijdeman, 1982 Nov (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Troelstra, 1982 Jun - 1983 Jan (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Van den Dries, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Van Heijenoort, 1982 Jun - Nov (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Wainer, 1982 Nov (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Weibel, 1982 Aug - 1983 Dec (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Weingartner, 1982 Jun - Dec (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Wilkie, 1982 Sep - Nov (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Wojcicki, 1982 Aug - Nov (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Wojtylak, 1982 Aug - Nov (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Zucker, 1982 Sep (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Early Drafts, 1983 Jan (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Evaluation (J. Owings), 1982 Oct (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Godel Obituary (Correspondence Regarding), 1982 Sep - Oct (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Lecture Notes, 1982 Oct (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Lecture (Unpublished): "Grundlagen der Mathematik'' (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1982 Feb - Nov (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Memos, 1982 Dec (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence with "Odd People", 1982 Feb - Nov (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Royal Society, 1982 Oct - Nov (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Anellis, 1983 Jan - Apr (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Arnon, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Baoz, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Barendregt, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Beeson, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Benacerraf, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Berlin, 1982 Dec - 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Cassels, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Cellucci, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Culik, 1983 Jan - Mar (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Dawson, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - del Franco, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Deligne, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Pelzell, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Dummet, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Engeler, 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Ershov (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Feferman, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Girard, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Godel, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Gurevich, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Hlawka, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Howard, 1983 Jan - Mar (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Jost, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Klcene, 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Kuiper, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Lenstra, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Longo, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Luckhardt, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - MacIntyre, 1983 Jan - Apr (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Mass, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Mazur (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Mints, 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Mondrijk, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Murdoch, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Nelson, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Peters, 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Piatelli-Palmarini, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Popper, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Pour-El, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Prasad, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, 1983 Jan (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Sacks (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Saledor, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Schmitterer, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Schraeder-Heister, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Scott, 1983 Mar - Apr (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Shepherdson, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Shiner, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Statma, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Stavi, 1983 Feb - Mar (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Takeuti, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Taussky-Todd, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Terlouw (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Troelstra, 1983 Jan - Apr (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Van den Dries, 1983 Mar (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Van Heijenoort (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Wainer, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Weibel, 1983 Apr (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Weingartner, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Wojtylak, 1983 Feb - Apr (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Essays and Drafts, no dates (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Evaluations (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Lecture Notes, 1983 Feb (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence with "Mad Persons" (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Royal Society, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - UNESCO Meeting on Artistotelian Logic (Letters Regarding) (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Godel Papers from the Hinisterium fur Innere und Kulturelle Angelegenheiten (Republik Osterreich, Osterreichisches Staatsarchiv) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Between Godel and his Mother (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Godel Paper: "Generalized Continuum Hypotheses" (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Sketches of Godel (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Godel's Proof of the Existence of God (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Comments from Godel's Dissertation Committee (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Almog, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Anellis, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Baaz, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Bellin, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Bethke, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Burge, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Burgess, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Cassel, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Cellucci, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dawson, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Davis, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - del Franco, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - del Franco, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Delzell, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Dyson, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Efron, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Engeler, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Ershov, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Farmer, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Feferman, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Follesdal, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Franova, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Geyer, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Girard, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Goad, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Godel, Kurt, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Godel, Rudolf, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Gordeer, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Halmos, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Hasenjager, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Hlawka, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Howard, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Jacobs, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Jager, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Jech, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Jeroslov, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Jockusch, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Jost, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Kleene, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Kolmogorov, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Krause, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Lacon, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Lenstra, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Le Veque, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Longo, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Luckhardt, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Leeb, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Lyndon, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - McCarthy, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - MacIntyre, Angus, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - MacIntyre, Angus, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - McRobbie, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - "Madmen", 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Manders, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Mints, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Moerdyk, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Murdoch, Iris, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Neurkirch, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Okada, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Paris, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Piattelli-Palmerini, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Pohlers, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Pour El, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Prawitz, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sabbagh, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Schimanoritch, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Schmetter, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Schroeder, Heister, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Schwichtenberg, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Scott, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Shepherdson, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Shiner, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Simpson, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Sinaceur, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Solomon, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Statman, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Stegmuller, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Stepanov, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Takeuti, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Taussky, Olga, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Taussky, Olga, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Tragesser, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Troelstra, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Van den Dreis, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Van den Hoeven, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Van Heij enoort, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Verdiglione, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Viertl, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Visser, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Wainer, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Weibel, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Weingartner, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Wojtylak, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Hustholz, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Yates, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Zassenhas, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Ziegler, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Contemporary Logic, mss, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Thinking About Man: Hardware, Software, and Wetware, Tokyo, mss, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Twentieth Century Philosophy of Mathematics, mss, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Lectures in Germany, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Royal Society Meeting, "Aspects of Gene Expression and Its Control", 1984 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Almog, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Anellis, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Baaz, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Crick, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Crossley, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - del Franco, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Delzell, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Dyson, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Etfron, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Engeler, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Feferman, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Hegeler Institute, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Friedman, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Geyer, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Götschel, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Hofmann, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Lopez-Escobar, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Longo, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Luckhardt, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - MacIntyre, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - "Mad Woman", 1984 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Malinowski, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - McCarty, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Morovisik, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Minto, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Murdoch, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Nedo, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Otte, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Salecker, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Scedrov, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Schimanovich, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Schmel, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Schwichteng, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Scott, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Shanker, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Simon, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Sinacuer, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Suppes, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Takeuti, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Taussky, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Tragesser, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Van Heijenoort, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Vissel, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Weingartner, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Wojtilach, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Yalom, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Yates, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Seminar, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Introduction to Philosophy (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Lectures (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Evaluations, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Letters to others about Godel (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Writings on/evaluations of Godel's work (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Royal Society obituary by Kreisel (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Interview with Kreisel about Godel (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Letters about the future of Godel's papers (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Godel from others (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Kreisel's memoir about Godel (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Drafts of the memoir (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Drafts of the memoir (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH_2015_100
  - Kreisel, Introduction to philosophy through problems in mathematics, (tss), c. 2, undated (Box 1)
- Evaluations
  - re A – H (includes "anonymous") (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - re I – O (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - re P – Z (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - re more than one individual (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Notes (Seminars, Lectures, etc. – published and unpublished), manuscripts, publications
  - Abstract structures [seminar notes] (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Algebraic proof theory [seminar notes] Autumn 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Applications of Proof Theory to Computer Science [technical report] (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Axiomatic Systems; Foundational Uses of Proof Theory [unpublished lectures] ca. 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Axiomatic Systems; Foundational Uses of Proof Theory [unpublished lectures] (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Computations and Formal Deductions; Markov's Principle (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Elementary Logic [lecture notes] (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Elements of Mathematical Logic: Model Theory by Krivine, Kreisel, 1967 [notes and revisions] (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Five Notes on Transfinite Progression [technical report], 1962-07-31 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Formal Rules and Questions of Justifying Mathematical Practices; What have we learned from Hilbert's Second Problem?; Some Purposes of Generalizing Recursive Theory [rough drafts] (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - French course [lecture notes], 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Memo to Barwise, Mints, Simpson, Statman, Stavi re research problems (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Metarecursion Theory (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Model Theory; AC; Bar Recursion [notes] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nervous System [lecture notes], 1954 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Non-uniqueness Results for Transfinite Progressions [technical report], 2/22/61 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Publications, correspondence regarding [North Holland Publishing co. and others] (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fundamental Concepts of Intuitionistic Mathematics, UCLA [lecture notes], 1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fundamental Concepts of Intuitionistic Mathematics, UCLA [lecture notes], 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Der unheilvolle Einbruch der Logik in die Mathematik [first lecture on Wittgenstin, manuscript] 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Weak Completeness of Intuitionistic Predicate Logic [technical report] and other articles 1/27/61 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Diary [problems and theorems], 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Diary [problems and theorems], 1962, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Articles/Lectures
    - Interpretations and Some Use, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Choice of normalization steps: a pedagogic example, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Explicit realization of existential theorems, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Models and functional interpretations, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Well orderings (transfinite induction) in proof theory, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - What is a recursively analytic function of a complex variable?, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - The meaning of Brouwer's free choice sequences, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Formalization of mathematical practice: analytic number theory, n.d. [written Hotel Bristol, Wien] (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Bertrand Russell: Critical or speculative philosopher? Leeds, 16 Oct. 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Some purposes of generalizing recursion theories [final draft], no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Modelltheorie und Unentscheidbarkeitsgrade, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Mechanical computability and physical realizability of sequences of natural numbers, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - [untitled] first line begins "I am interested here in the refinements of.. .model theory and recursion theory.. ." n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Denkpsychologische Betrachtungen im Gebiete der mathematischen Mengenlehre, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Explicit mathematics and explicit metamathematics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Applications of model theory and proof theory, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Metamathematical principles needed to establish closure properties of formal systems, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Memo: A retrogression tendency in the study of abstract logics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - A neglected aspect of the formalization of informal mathematics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Two specific problems in intuitionistic mathematics and metamathematics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Computer Science begins where recursion theory ends, no date> (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - History of Logic Symposium, Dec. 27, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Consumer Guide to Proof Theory, no date> (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Philosophy of Mathematics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Logic in the Sixties (5.2.73) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Wie kam man dazu, Beweise nach ihrem Inhalt zu normalisieren? (Muenchen 15.1.73) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - What use are normal derivations in (classical) analysis?, no date> (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Begriff des formalen Systems; formale mechanische Operationen an endlichen Woertern.. ." n.d. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Was leistet die Formalisierung der modelltheoretischen Metamathematik? (Muenster, 25.1.73) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Was sind und was sollen die Funktionalinterpretationen? (Kiel, 26.1.73) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Wie die Beweistheorie zu ihren Ordinalzahlen kam, (Hannover, 19.1.73) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Additions to REVIEW (of course notes, 1973) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Further additions to REVIEW (of course notes, 1973) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - What do we want to know about constructive mathematics? Aug. 1, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Conflicting requirements on formalizations of a branch of mathematics, no date> (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - b - models: a model theory for the schema WF[R] ® TI[R,A], no date> (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Notions without a definite extension, no date> (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - [untitled] first line begins: "This note supplements the translator's sketch.. ." (re Gentzen), no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Facts and fantasies about logic in philosophy, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Natural representations of concepts and natural equivalence, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Applications of non-standard semantics, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - On studying the history of philosophy, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy of mathematics and the Silent Majority, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Natural representation and identity criteria of concepts, no date> (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - [untitled notes] first line begins: "I thought of calling this lecture Formalist principles of mathematics versus principles of formalist mathematics," n.d. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Formal systems complete for Goedel's functional interpretation (course notes Autumn 1969) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Seminar notes: Autumn 1969 – Review (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - What is lost by formalist foundations?, nd. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Lecture 1 – “The origins of mathematics certainly lie…” [contains proofs of the “fundamental theorem of algebra”] n.d. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Lecture 2 – “We recall that we mentioned ‘formally-real’ fiends” n.d. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Equality between simple functionals, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Effective versions of proofs in analytic number theory, nd. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Elements of mathematical logic (I. Semantic study of classical logic), no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Technical progress and the problems of philosophy, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Model theoretic meaning of recursive sets and effective operations, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Preface [to a book on mathematical logic?] and B. Foundational problems, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Using ordinals instead of cardinals for analyzing (infinite) prepositional logic, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Existential assumptions and their languages, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Review of Seminar [no further title, n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Infinitary languages of n-ary relations, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Inductive definitions, hierarchies and subclasses of the class of recursive functions, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Appendix B: Completeness of intuitionistic predicate logic, n.d. [also, Italian translation] (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The greatest goof for the greatest number, no date> (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Two notes on the foundations of set theory, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - On the relationship between intuitionistic and classical arithmetic (appendix I), n.d. [on verso: handwritten MS, discussion of biological phenomena and consciousness] (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Miscellany
  - International Congress of Logicians and Mathematicians, Nice, correspondence re, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Logicians and Mathematicians, Nice, correspondence re, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Logicians and Mathematicians, Nice, correspondence re, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Logicians and Mathematicians, Helsinki, correspondence re [this is either folder 5 or 5a – original list unclear], 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5a)
  - Philosophy Department, Stanford University (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified fragments of letters, papers, etc. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Notes, manuscripts, lectures, publications
  - Memo concerning mathematical properties of ECF, ICF, etc. Christmas 1975. BR, neighborhood functions and the theory of species., 1976-02-10 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Brouwer, L. E. J. – earlier drafts and correspondence re Kreisel’s 2nd Brouwer review (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Metamathematik mit Beschraenkten Mitteln: Modellund Beweistheorie. [lecture] Muenchen, 1975-04-06 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Wittgenstein – drafts and correspondence re Kreisel’s 2nd lecture on Wittgenstein, “Proofs and rules: topics for illustrating Wittgenstein’s style of thought.”, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Course notes, memorandum (Spring 1976)
  - “Half-stage Lessons” (Spring quarter 1976) [course notes] (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - “Comments on the papers with Mints and Simpson in Springer Lecture Notes 453 (1975) pp. 38-131” (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Wittgenstein colloquim, 1976 Apr
  - Correspondence re Kreisel’s paper on Wittgenstein; preliminary versions (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence re publication of Wittgenstein Colloquium paper (Box 26, Folder 2a)
  - Memos/course notes:
    - “Realizations and realizability” (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - “Modelling Intuitionistic implicational logic by means of hereditarily formalized proofs and operations” Aut. 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - “Formal system for ILL” (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - “Questions related to the regular operators of Dean McCullogh” (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - “Data for analytic functions” (Box 26, Folder 3)